{"First Name_{}":{"question":"First Name","answer":"Pranesh","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"Middle Name_{}":{"question":"Middle Name","answer":"Subhash","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"Last Name_{}":{"question":"Last Name","answer":"Nangare","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"Current Location_{}":{"question":"Current Location","answer":"Pune","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"Have you ever worked for Cimpress/Vista company before?_{\"Yes\":\"Yes\",\"No\":\"No\"}":{"question":"Have you ever worked for Cimpress/Vista company before?","answer":["NA"],"options":{"Yes":"Yes","No":"No"},"type":"Radio Button"},"Will you now or in the future require sponsorship for employment visa status?_{\"Yes\":\"Yes\",\"No\":\"No\"}":{"question":"Will you now or in the future require sponsorship for employment visa status?","answer":"No","options":{"Yes":"Yes","No":"No"},"type":"Radio Button"},"Do you have an employment card not sponsored by Cimpress/Vistaprint?_{\"Yes\":\"Yes\",\"No\":\"No\"}":{"question":"Do you have an employment card not sponsored by Cimpress/Vistaprint?","answer":"No","options":{"Yes":"Yes","No":"No"},"type":"Radio Button"},"Data Privacy Policy Consent_{\"<span class=\\\"ui-provider a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z ab ac ae af ag ah ai aj ak\\\" dir=\\\"ltr\\\">I consent to the <a aria-label=\\\"Link Privacy Policy\\\" href=\\\"https://careers.vista.com/wp-content/themes/careers.vista.com/assets/docs/privacy-policy.pdf\\\" rel=\\\"noreferrer noopener\\\" target=\\\"_blank\\\" class=\\\"fui-Link ___1rxvrpe f2hkw1w f3rmtva f1ewtqcl fyind8e f1k6fduh f1w7gpdv fk6fouc fjoy568 figsok6 f1hu3pq6 f11qmguv f19f4twv f1tyq0we f1g0x7ka fhxju0i f1qch9an f1cnd47f fqv5qza f1vmzxwi f1o700av f13mvf36 f1cmlufx f9n3di6 f1ids18y f1tx3yz7 f1deo86v f1eh06m1 f1iescvh fhgqx19 f1olyrje f1p93eir f1nev41a f1h8hb77 f1lqvz6u f10aw75t fsle3fq f17ae5zn\\\" title=\\\"https://careers.vista.com/wp-content/themes/careers.vista.com/assets/docs/privacy-policy.pdf\\\">Privacy Policy</a></span>\":\"<span class=\\\"ui-provider a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z ab ac ae af ag ah ai aj ak\\\" dir=\\\"ltr\\\">I consent to the <a aria-label=\\\"Link Privacy Policy\\\" href=\\\"https://careers.vista.com/wp-content/themes/careers.vista.com/assets/docs/privacy-policy.pdf\\\" rel=\\\"noreferrer noopener\\\" target=\\\"_blank\\\" class=\\\"fui-Link ___1rxvrpe f2hkw1w f3rmtva f1ewtqcl fyind8e f1k6fduh f1w7gpdv fk6fouc fjoy568 figsok6 f1hu3pq6 f11qmguv f19f4twv f1tyq0we f1g0x7ka fhxju0i f1qch9an f1cnd47f fqv5qza f1vmzxwi f1o700av f13mvf36 f1cmlufx f9n3di6 f1ids18y f1tx3yz7 f1deo86v f1eh06m1 f1iescvh fhgqx19 f1olyrje f1p93eir f1nev41a f1h8hb77 f1lqvz6u f10aw75t fsle3fq f17ae5zn\\\" title=\\\"https://careers.vista.com/wp-content/themes/careers.vista.com/assets/docs/privacy-policy.pdf\\\">Privacy Policy</a></span>\"}":{"question":"Data Privacy Policy Consent","answer":"I have read and understood the Data Privacy Policy and I consent to the processing of my personal data as described in the Policy.","options":{"<span class=\"ui-provider a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z ab ac ae af ag ah ai aj ak\" dir=\"ltr\">I consent to the <a aria-label=\"Link Privacy Policy\" href=\"https://careers.vista.com/wp-content/themes/careers.vista.com/assets/docs/privacy-policy.pdf\" rel=\"noreferrer noopener\" target=\"_blank\" class=\"fui-Link ___1rxvrpe f2hkw1w f3rmtva f1ewtqcl fyind8e f1k6fduh f1w7gpdv fk6fouc fjoy568 figsok6 f1hu3pq6 f11qmguv f19f4twv f1tyq0we f1g0x7ka fhxju0i f1qch9an f1cnd47f fqv5qza f1vmzxwi f1o700av f13mvf36 f1cmlufx f9n3di6 f1ids18y f1tx3yz7 f1deo86v f1eh06m1 f1iescvh fhgqx19 f1olyrje f1p93eir f1nev41a f1h8hb77 f1lqvz6u f10aw75t fsle3fq f17ae5zn\" title=\"https://careers.vista.com/wp-content/themes/careers.vista.com/assets/docs/privacy-policy.pdf\">Privacy Policy</a></span>":"<span class=\"ui-provider a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z ab ac ae af ag ah ai aj ak\" dir=\"ltr\">I consent to the <a aria-label=\"Link Privacy Policy\" href=\"https://careers.vista.com/wp-content/themes/careers.vista.com/assets/docs/privacy-policy.pdf\" rel=\"noreferrer noopener\" target=\"_blank\" class=\"fui-Link ___1rxvrpe f2hkw1w f3rmtva f1ewtqcl fyind8e f1k6fduh f1w7gpdv fk6fouc fjoy568 figsok6 f1hu3pq6 f11qmguv f19f4twv f1tyq0we f1g0x7ka fhxju0i f1qch9an f1cnd47f fqv5qza f1vmzxwi f1o700av f13mvf36 f1cmlufx f9n3di6 f1ids18y f1tx3yz7 f1deo86v f1eh06m1 f1iescvh fhgqx19 f1olyrje f1p93eir f1nev41a f1h8hb77 f1lqvz6u f10aw75t fsle3fq f17ae5zn\" title=\"https://careers.vista.com/wp-content/themes/careers.vista.com/assets/docs/privacy-policy.pdf\">Privacy Policy</a></span>"},"type":"acceptance"},"What is your notice period?_{\"0\":\"15 Days or less\",\"1\":\"1 Month\",\"2\":\"2 Months\",\"3\":\"3 Months\",\"4\":\"More than 3 Months\",\"5\":\"Serving Notice Period\"}":{"question":"What is your notice period?","answer":["2 Months"],"options":{"0":"15 Days or less","1":"1 Month","2":"2 Months","3":"3 Months","4":"More than 3 Months","5":"Serving Notice Period"},"type":"List Menu"},"What is your expected CTC in Lakhs per annum?_{}":{"question":"What is your expected CTC in Lakhs per annum?","answer":"13 LPA","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"How many years of experience do you have in Node.Js?_{}":{"question":"How many years of experience do you have in Node.Js?","answer":"3","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"How many years of experience do you have in React.Js?_{}":{"question":"How many years of experience do you have in React.Js?","answer":"3 Years","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"How many years of experience do you have in any Database?_{}":{"question":"How many years of experience do you have in any Database?","answer":"3 years","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"How many years of experience do you have in typescript?_{}":{"question":"How many years of experience do you have in typescript?","answer":"3","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"Preferred Location_{}":{"question":"Preferred Location","answer":"Pune / Bangalore / Mumbai","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"Highest Qualification_{\"Pre Graduation\":\"Pre Graduation\",\"Graduation\":\"Graduation\",\"Post Graduation\":\"Post Graduation\",\"Diploma\":\"Diploma\",\"Doctorate\":\"Doctorate\"}":{"question":"Highest Qualification","answer":["Graduation"],"options":{"Pre Graduation":"Pre Graduation","Graduation":"Graduation","Post Graduation":"Post Graduation","Diploma":"Diploma","Doctorate":"Doctorate"},"type":"List Menu"},"Notice Period_{\"Immediate\":\"Immediate\",\"0-15 Days\":\"0-15 Days\",\"15-30 Days\":\"15-30 Days\",\"30-60 Days\":\"30-60 Days\",\"90 Days\":\"90 Days\"}":{"question":"Notice Period","answer":["30-60 Days"],"options":{"Immediate":"Immediate","0-15 Days":"0-15 Days","15-30 Days":"15-30 Days","30-60 Days":"30-60 Days","90 Days":"90 Days"},"type":"List Menu"},"Current CTC (Numeric Input Only)_{}":{"question":"Current CTC (Numeric Input Only)","answer":"850000","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"Expected CTC (Numeric Input Only)_{}":{"question":"Expected CTC (Numeric Input Only)","answer":"1200000","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"What is your current CTC in Lakhs per annum?_{}":{"question":"What is your current CTC in Lakhs per annum?","answer":"8.5 LPA","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"What is your notice period?_{}":{"question":"What is your notice period?","answer":"2 Months","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"How many years of experience do you have in Javascript?_{}":{"question":"How many years of experience do you have in Javascript?","answer":"3 Years","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"How many years of experience do you have in Html/Css?_{}":{"question":"How many years of experience do you have in Html/Css?","answer":"3 Years","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"Please select the city you are currently residing or willing to relocate to_{\"0\":\"Ahmedabad\",\"1\":\"Vadodara, Gujarat\",\"2\":\"Pune, Maharashtra\"}":{"question":"Please select the city you are currently residing or willing to relocate to","answer":["Pune","Bangalore","Mumbai"],"options":{"0":"Ahmedabad","1":"Vadodara, Gujarat","2":"Pune, Maharashtra"},"type":"Check Box"},"How many years of experience do you have in Ecmascript 6?_{}":{"question":"How many years of experience do you have in Ecmascript 6?","answer":"0","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"How many years of experience do you have in HTML?_{}":{"question":"How many years of experience do you have in HTML?","answer":"3 Years","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"How many years of experience do you have in Nextjs?_{}":{"question":"How many years of experience do you have in Nextjs?","answer":"0","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"How many years of experience do you have in Typescript?_{}":{"question":"How many years of experience do you have in Typescript?","answer":["0"],"options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"Are you currently residing in Pune, Maharashtra or willing to relocate to Pune, Maharashtra?_{\"0\":\"Yes\",\"1\":\"No\"}":{"question":"Are you currently residing in Pune, Maharashtra or willing to relocate to Pune, Maharashtra?","answer":["Yes"],"options":{"0":"Yes","1":"No"},"type":"Radio Button"},"How many years of experience do you have in Angular_{}":{"question":"How many years of experience do you have in Angular","answer":"0","options":{},"type":"Text Box"},"Which version of Angular you have used in last project_{\"newOption1\":\"Angular 15+\",\"newOption2\":\"Angular 12 -14\",\"newOption3\":\"Angular 11 and below\"}":{"question":"Which version of Angular you have used in last project","answer":[],"options":{"newOption1":"Angular 15+","newOption2":"Angular 12 -14","newOption3":"Angular 11 and below"},"type":"Radio Button"}}